PAULA DA SILVA

Junior Frontend Software Developer

carolpaulag@gmail.com • +353 083 0375541 • Leitrim
GitHub • LinkedIn • Portfolio • STAMP 4

Executive Summary

Junior Software Developer with a Diploma in Full stack Software Development from the Code Institute. proficient in HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python. I have 7 years experience in Finance. I am a valuable team-player with strong communication skills and effective problem solving ability. I am eager to gain entry into the tech industry into an exciting development team where I can grow and contribute!

Education

Apr 2022 - Apr 2023 Code Institute Dublin, Ireland (Remote)

Diploma in Fullstack Software Development (Accredited by the University West of Scotland)

Jan 2014 – Dez 2017 Paulista University

Bachelor of Finance Management

Technical Skillset

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Python, React

Databases: MySQL, Postgres

Frameworks: Django, Jquery, Bootstrap

Version Control: Git, Github

UX Tools: Figma, Balsamiq

Portfolio projects

- 1. Fresh-E-Mart A small shop that sells the best and most varied selection of fruits and organics. Technologies Used HTML5 and CSS. GitHub https://github.com/paulasdev/Fresh-E-Mart
- 2. Quiz Factor An online interactive learning game to test you knowledge in 4 different categories Technologies Used HTML5 , CSS and JavaScrip. GitHub https://github.com/paulasdev/quiz-factor
- 3. BrickLib Add, create, edit and delete bricks to track, organize and share collections with others users. Technologies Used CRUD operations using HTML5 , CSS with Bootstrap, Python, Django framework. GitHub https://github.com/paulasdev/BrickLib
- 4. The Brunch Basket A premier online marketplace for brunch lovers. Technologies Used E-Commerce site, built using Django, Python, Stripe, AWS, JQuery, HTML and CSS. GitHub https://github.com/paulasdev/The_Brunch_Basket

Collaborative Projects

Hackathon - An online community that has overcome the language barrier, allowing its users to spark up conversations with anyone from all over the globe! <u>Getting Connected</u> - We placed 2nd in this collaborative project.

Work Experience

April 2022 - Present Student: Fullstack Software Development (ECommerce)

Code Institute

Career break to upskill

November 2021–March 2022 Future Cast, Digital Marketing Assistant

Manorhamilton, Co. Leitrim, Ireland

- Built out new Google Ads Campaigns utilising proper account structure and best practices. Managed a Google Ads account to meet short term optimization goals.
- Built SEO Optimized WordPress Website

June 2019 - October 2021 Maternity Leave

• Career break for maternity leave

July 2017 - January 2019 Child Minder

Relocation to Ireland from Brazil to improve my English skills and to pursue international exposure.

July 2015 - February 2017 Accounts Payable Analyst

Caixa Seguradora, Brazil

- Kept all accounts up to date and ensure any queries/invoice issues are actioned.
- Sent invoices out for approval and following up with outstanding approvals
- Assisted in the preparing of weekly payment
- Processed 800 weekly invoices on SAP

June 2011 - February 2015 Accounts Receivable Analyst

PDG Incorporadora, Brazil

- Monitored the migration of data between the operating system and ERP system, in addition to keeping 200 bank accounts reconciled in the ERP system through daily bank files.
- Responsible for the team's support for the accuracy of reconciliations between companies and for the accuracy of transactions between companies.
- Assisted other members of the finance team in maintaining internal controls, systems and processes and with annual external audit queries
- Prepared month-end balance sheet reconciliations.
- Troubleshooting problems with financial systems
- Collected and analysed numerous unidentified payments, resulting in a 60% reduction in delinquency of my assigned target.

Additional Information

- I attend regular 'women in tech' networking events.
- Fluent Portuguese, Fluent English